RAVIS SAVOY

STUDENT AT AIE(ACADEMY OF INTERACTIVE ENTERTAINMENT)

EMAIL: ravissavoy@gmail.com

LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/ravissavov GITHUB: RavisSavov47

SUMMARY

I'm a game programmer with 2 years of experience in coding languages such as C++ and C#, as well as being experienced in engines such as Unity and Unreal. I've worked on many small projects some of which was working in a team. In these projects, my main focus was on the creation of major gameplay features, such as time management and the behavior of enemies.

EDUCATION

Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE)

Aug. 2021 - Dec. 2023

Associate's Degree Game Programming 2023

EMPLOYMENT

Raising Cane's, Certified Traner, New Iberia, Louisiana

Aug. 2021 - Current, Aug. 2021 - Current

I provide personalized training to cane's members, helping them learn our industry standards. This involves teaching proper techniques, emphasizing safety, and tracking progress, all within a supportive environment at Raisins Canes.

SKILLS

EXPERIENCED IN: Unreal, Unity, C#, C++, GitHub, Perforce,

Project Management

PROJECTS

B-Force

Jan. 2023 - June 2023

It's my second year project from AIE, that I worked with a group of 6 people over the course of 5 months using Unreal engine. It's a fast paced racing game where you control a bee on a backyard track. I was mainly involved in the creation of some major gameplay features like obstacles and time Managers.

Yokai Invasion

May 2022 - June 2022

It was my first experience in working on a small production with a group created in Unity. It's a classic horde shooter where your goal is to survive the endless waves of yokai. While working on this game, I was the one who focused on the creation of main gameplay features like player's attacks, power-Up system, and enemy behaviors.